[{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14987,"timeElapsed":120073},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11014,"timeElapsed":131090},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4244,"timeElapsed":135337},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4902,"timeElapsed":140241},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3890,"timeElapsed":144133},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":13325,"timeElapsed":157461},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5794,"timeElapsed":163251},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9778,"timeElapsed":173025},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7000,"timeElapsed":180025},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7799,"timeElapsed":189384},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8892,"timeElapsed":198277},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4933,"timeElapsed":203211},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4328,"timeElapsed":207541},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3153,"timeElapsed":210696},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":30420,"timeElapsed":241117},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":16577,"timeElapsed":257696},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8307,"timeElapsed":266006},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4222,"timeElapsed":270230},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":10362,"timeElapsed":282083},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":38085,"timeElapsed":320171},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":24493,"timeElapsed":344666},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2457,"timeElapsed":347125},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2926,"timeElapsed":350053},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4005,"timeElapsed":354060},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6650,"timeElapsed":360712},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4330,"timeElapsed":365044},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":366781},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9801,"timeElapsed":377776},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3461,"timeElapsed":381239},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3113,"timeElapsed":384354},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4765,"timeElapsed":389121},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":392454},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":75378,"timeElapsed":467835},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2621,"timeElapsed":470458},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3988,"timeElapsed":474448},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2766,"timeElapsed":477216},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7160,"timeElapsed":513709},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710860,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5481,"timeElapsed":519191},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":9233,"timeElapsed":528427},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4198,"timeElapsed":532627},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2854,"timeElapsed":535482},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2280,"timeElapsed":537765},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3754,"timeElapsed":541521},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2514,"timeElapsed":544037},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3996,"timeElapsed":548035},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1964,"timeElapsed":550001},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7313,"timeElapsed":561813},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":566946},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":23207,"timeElapsed":590155},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3024,"timeElapsed":593181},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":67813,"timeElapsed":660995},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4325,"timeElapsed":665323},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1908,"timeElapsed":667233},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4352,"timeElapsed":671588},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3218,"timeElapsed":674808},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":5417,"timeElapsed":681660},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9554,"timeElapsed":691216},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":694937},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980889924,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3317,"timeElapsed":698256},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3982,"timeElapsed":702240},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":705783},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4019,"timeElapsed":709804},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980904322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2847,"timeElapsed":712653},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980907607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3283,"timeElapsed":715938},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":718376},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5436,"timeElapsed":725246},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":23180,"timeElapsed":748428},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":19323,"timeElapsed":767754},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":12904,"timeElapsed":780659},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980975256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2926,"timeElapsed":783588},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2547,"timeElapsed":786137},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980979627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1819,"timeElapsed":787959},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":12250,"timeElapsed":800211},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":802567},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3905,"timeElapsed":807487},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":29806,"timeElapsed":837295},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2572,"timeElapsed":839869},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":842887},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981038780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":847112},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4174,"timeElapsed":851289},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981045019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":853351},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981049561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4540,"timeElapsed":857893},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981051735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2172,"timeElapsed":860067},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981057923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5092,"timeElapsed":866255},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2305,"timeElapsed":868562},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981063249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":871581},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981065667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2417,"timeElapsed":873999},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4240,"timeElapsed":878242},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981073633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3721,"timeElapsed":881965},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2075,"timeElapsed":884042},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2684,"timeElapsed":886729},{"subjectID":"eyalypqqkv","prolificID":"665c19ed6674d8ab7f616b65","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b231cb1517e444d1dd13","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":888980}]